export const quizData = [
    {
      id: 0,
      question: ` What is the result of the following expression: typeof([])? `,
      options: [`object`, `array`, `undefined`,`string`],
      answer: `object`
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `Which of the following is used to iterate over the properties of an object?`,
      options: [`or of`, `foreach`, `for in`,`iterate`],
      answer: `for in`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `What is the purpose of the JSON.stringify() method in JavaScript?`,
      options: [`Parses a JSON string to a JavaScript object`,
       `Removes an element from an array`, 
       ` Sorts the elements of an array`,
       `Converts a JavaScript object to a JSON string`],
      answer: `Converts a JavaScript object to a JSON string`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `What does the === operator do in JavaScript?`,
      options: [` Assigns a value to a variable`, 
      `Compares values for equality with type coercion`, 
      ` Compares values for equality without type coercion`,
      `Checks if a variable is declared`],
      answer: ` Compares values for equality without type coercion`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `Which method is used to add a new element to the end of an array?`,
      options: [` append()`, `addToEnd()`, `concat()`,`push()`],
      answer: `push()`
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `Which event is triggered when a user clicks on an HTML element?`,
      options: [` onhover `, `onclick`, `onchange`,`onsubmit`],
      answer: `onclick`
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `What is the purpose of the try...catch statement in JavaScript?`,
      options: [` Creates a conditional statement`, `Declares a new variable`, `Defines a loop`,`Handles exceptions and errors`],
      answer: `Handles exceptions and errors`
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `How can you prevent the default behavior of an HTML form submission in JavaScript?`,
      options: [` event.stopImmediatePropagation()`, `event.preventDefault()`, `event.stopPropagation()`,`event.defaultPrevented()`],
      answer: `event.preventDefault()`
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `What is the purpose of the querySelector method in JavaScript?`,
      options: [` Retrieves the first element that matches a specified CSS selector `,
       `Selects all elements that match a specified CSS selector`,
       `Creates a new HTML element`,
      `Modifies the style of an HTML element`],
      answer: ` Retrieves the first element that matches a specified CSS selector`
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `Which keyword is used to declare a constant in JavaScript?`,
      options: [` var`, `let`, `const`,`static`],
      answer: `const`
    },   
  ];
  